Guide to Don Oberdorfer's Mansfield Biography Research Papers 1918-2003
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Audio Interviews with Mansfield's Colleagues, 1998-2001; Series III; 41 audio cassettes
  - Interview with Richard Holbrooke - RESTRICTED, April 20, 1999 (Cassette III-11)
  - Interview with Norvill Jones, May 1, 1999; Audio quality very poor so the cassette is not digitized. (Cassette III-12)
  - Interview with Peggy DeMichele, July 26, 1999 (Cassette III-13)
  - Interview with John Mansfield - RESTRICTED, September 2, 1999 (Cassette III-14)
  - Interview with James "Jim" Lowenstein, October 1, 1999 (Cassette III-15)
  - Interview with John Finney - RESTRICTED, November 5, 1999 (Cassette III-16)
  - Interview with Francis "Frank" Valeo, November 29, 1999 (Cassette III-17)
  - Interview with Francis "Frank" Valeo, November 29, 1999 (Cassette III-18)
  - Interview with Sam Jameson, January 1, 2000 (Cassette III-19)
  - Interview with Justin Bloom - RESTRICTED, February 4, 2000 (Cassette III-20)
  - Interview with Michael Armacost - RESTRICTED, February 21, 2000 (Cassette III-21)
  - Interview with Walter "Fritz" Mondale - RESTRICTED, March 14, 2000 (Cassette III-22)
  - Interview with Bob Strauss - RESTRICTED, March 27, 2000 (Cassette III-23)
  - Interview with Robert "Bob" McNamara - RESTRICTED; Interview with Jack Valenti - RESTRICTED, October 11, 2000; October 7, 2000 (Cassette III-24)
  - Interview with Pat Holt - RESTRICTED, August 2, 2001 (Cassette III-25)
  - Interview with Bobby Baker - RESTRICTED, December 31, 2001 (Cassette III-26)
  - Interview with Bob Brown, March 13, circa 2000; Audio quality very poor so the cassette is not digitized. (Cassette III-27)
  - Interview with Ray Dockstader, circa 2000 (Cassette III-28)
  - Interview with Michael Armacost - RESTRICTED, February 7, 2000 (Cassette III-29)
  - Interview with Chester Cooper - RESTRICTED, November 24, circa 2000; This cassette tape contains two separate interviews with unidentified speakers. It isn't clear which speaker is Cooper. (Cassette III-30)
  - Interview with George McGovern, February 1, 2002 (Cassette III-31)
  - Interview with Leslie "Les" Gelb - RESTRICTED, October 1, 1999; This cassette tape also contains an interview the Don Oberdorfer conducted with Nicholas Platt on October 1, 1993. The interview is not about Mike Mansfield. (Cassette III-32)
  - Interview with Kazutoshi Hasegawa - RESTRICTED, November 16, 1998 (Cassette III-33)
  - Interview with Fukuchima (first name unknown) - RESTRICTED, November 20, 1998; This cassette tape contains two separate interviews with unidentified speakers. It isn't clear who either of the interviewees are. It's also not clear if the name written on the tape label is an interviewee or the location of the interview. (Cassette III-34)
  - Interview with Takako Doi, December 1, 1998; Interviewee speaks Japanese. Audio quality very poor so the cassette is not digitized. (Cassette III-35)
  - Interview with Richard "Dick" Allen - RESTRICTED, October 27, 1999 (Cassette III-36)
  - Interview with James Auer - RESTRICTED, November 1, 1999 (Cassette III-37)
  - Interview with Salpee Sahagian - RESTRICTED, November 4, 1999 (Cassette III-38)
  - Interview with Kaiku (first name unknown) - RESTRICTED, March 1, 2000; Interviewee speaks Japanese. (Cassette III-39)
  - Interview with Mike Gravel - RESTRICTED, circa 2000 (Cassette III-40)
  - Interview with Albert Seligmann - RESTRICTED, circa 2000 (Cassette III-41)
- Audio Recordings, 1980-2000 and undated; Series IV; 10 audio cassettes
  This series contains miscellaneous audio recordings related to Oberdorfer’s research for his biography on Mansfield.
  Electronic copies of some of the audio are available from the University of Montana's Archives and Special Collections.
  - Mike Mansfield speaking to the Takeyama Association, February 17, 1986 (Cassette IV-1)
  - Meeting, possibly in Japan with Mike Mansfield or speaking about Mike Mansfield, June 12, 1986; Most of the audio in Japanese. (Cassette IV-2)
  - Mike Mansfield's remarks to Drexel Lambert, November 11, 1986 (Cassette IV-3)
  - Mike Mansfield speaking, possibly to the Midwest U.S. Japan Association, November 17, 1986 (Cassette IV-4)
  - Vietnam Dialogue call to Mike Mansfield with Don Oberdorfer and Phil (no last name) in attendance, June 18, 1998 (Cassette IV-5)
  - Funeral mass for Maureen Mansfield, September 26, 2000 (Cassette IV-6)
  - Mike Mansfield interviewed for article about U.S.-Japan cooperative relations, undated (Cassette IV-7)
  - Joint House and Senate administration hearing, Tape 1 of 2, March 18, 1999 (Cassette IV-8)
  - Joint House and Senate administration hearing, Tape 2 of 2, March 18, 1999 (Cassette IV-9)
  - Mike Mansfield interviewed by John Needham, August 13, 1980 (Cassette IV-10)